Love Unscripted
Accidentally Engaged is a comedy, romance, tv movie
film directed by Letia Clouston.
When unsuccessful actress Clarissa returns to her hometown for a wedding and tries to impress her old friends by claiming she's dating big time celebrity Chas Hunter, she
suddenly finds herself in a comically false engagement when her lies go public and Chas decides to join the festivities in a stunt to escape bad press.
Clarissa Byers, played by Lexi Giovagnoli.
Maya Wilton, played by Lexi Atkins.
Graham, played by Randy Wayne.
Jeannette, played by Maureen McCormick.
Sandy Byers, played by Joan Severance.
Chas Hunter, played by Brant Daugherty.
Peter Facinelli ( fa-chə-NELI; born November 26,
1973) is an American-Italian actor.
He starred as Donovan "Van" Ray on the Fox series Fastlane from 2002 to 2003.
He played Dr.
Carlisle Cullen in the film adaptations of the Twilight novel series, and is also
known for his role as Mike Dexter in the 1998 film Can't Hardly Wait.
Facinelli was a regular on the Showtime comedy-drama series
Nurse Jackie, portraying the role of Dr.
Fitch "Coop" Cooper.
He portrayed Maxwell Lord on the first season of the TV series Supergirl.
The film explores themes of celebrity, wedding,
hometown, lying, pretend relationship.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.